questionList = questionList.concat([
	//Past
	{question:"The boy ate.", answers:["El niño comió."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño comió.", answers:["The boy ate.", "The child ate."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was an apple.", answers:["Era una manzana.", "Fue una manzana."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era una manzana.", answers:["It was an apple."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Fue una mujer.", answers:["It was a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was a woman.", answers:["Fue una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era una mujer.", answers:["She was a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Ella era una mujer.", answers:["She was a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She was a woman.", answers:["Era una mujer.", "Ella era una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted era una niña.", answers:["You were a girl.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú eras una niña.", answers:["You were a girl.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eras una niña.", answers:["You were a girl.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were a child.", answers:["Usted era una niña.", "Tú eras una niña.", "Eras una niña.","Usted era un niño.", "Tú eras un niño.", "Eras un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You were a girl.", answers:["Usted era una niña.", "Tú eras una niña.", "Eras una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It was a girl.", answers:["Fue una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It was a child.", answers:["Fue una niña.", "Fue un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Fue una niña.", answers:["It was a child.", "It was a girl."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Usted era un niño.", answers:["You were a boy.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú eras un niño.", answers:["You were a boy.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Eras un niño.", answers:["You were a boy.", "You were a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were a boy.", answers:["Usted era un niño.", "Tú eras un niño.", "Eras un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It was a boy.", answers:["Fue un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Fue un niño.", answers:["It was a child.", "It was a boy."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Fue un hombre.", answers:["It was a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was a man.", answers:["Fue un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era un hombre.", answers:["He was a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Él era un hombre.", answers:["He was a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He was a man.", answers:["Era un hombre.", "Él era un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El hombre comió.", answers:["The man ate."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man ate.", answers:["El hombre comió."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú bebiste agua.", answers:["You drank water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo comí.", answers:["I ate."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I ate.", answers:["Comí.","Yo comí."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño bebió.", answers:["A boy drank.","A child drank"], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy drank.", answers:["Un niño bebió."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo bebí.", answers:["I drank."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I drank.", answers:["Yo bebí.", "Bebí."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comiste.", answers:["You ate."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You ate.", answers:["Tú comiste.", "Comiste.", "Usted comió."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era pan.", answers:["It was bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Fue pan.", answers:["It was bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was bread.", answers:["Fue pan.", "Era pan."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Era agua.", answers:["It was water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Fue agua.", answers:["It was water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It was water.", answers:["Era agua.", "Fue agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You were boys.", answers:["Ustedes eran niños."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes eran niños.", answers:["You were boys.","You were children."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Éramos niños.", answers:["We were boys.","We were children."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We were boys.", answers:["Éramos niños.", "Nosotros éramos niños."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Éramos niñas.", answers:["We were girls.","We were children."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We were girls.", answers:["Nosotras éramos niñas.", "Éramos niñas."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebimos leche.", answers:["We drank milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebimos leche.", answers:["We drank milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We drank milk.", answers:["Bebimos leche.", "Nosotros bebimos leche.", "Nosotras bebimos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras bebimos agua.", answers:["We drank water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros bebimos agua.", answers:["We drank water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We drank water.", answers:["Bebimos agua.", "Nosotros bebimos agua.", "Nosotras bebimos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You were girls.", answers:["Ustedes eran niñas."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes eran niñas.", answers:["You were girls.","You were children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotras éramos niñas.", answers:["We were girls.","We were children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Ellas eran niñas.", answers:["They were girls.","They were children."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They were girls.", answers:["Ellas eran niñas.","Eran niñas."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You drank water.", answers:["Tú bebiste agua.", "Bebiste agua.", "Usted bebió agua.", "Ustedes bebieron agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes bebieron agua.", answers:["You drank water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"You drank milk.", answers:["Tú bebiste leche.","Bebiste leche.","Usted bebió leche.","Ustedes bebieron leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotros éramos niños.", answers:["We were boys.","We were children."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We were boys.", answers:["Nosotros éramos niños.","Éramos niños."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They drank.", answers:["Bebieron.","Ellos bebieron.","Ellas bebieron."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos bebieron.", answers:["They drank."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas bebieron agua.", answers:["The girls drank water.","The children drank water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls drank water.", answers:["Las niñas bebieron agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños bebieron agua.", answers:["The boys drank water.","The children drank water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys drank water.", answers:["Los niños bebieron agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Tú escribiste un libro.", answers:["You wrote a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You wrote a book.", answers:["Tú escribiste un libro.","Escribiste un libro.","Usted escribió un libro.","Ustedes escribieron un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribió un libro.", answers:["You wrote a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribí una carta.", answers:["I wrote a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I wrote a letter.", answers:["Yo escribí una carta.","Escribí una carta."], language:"Spanish"},			
	{question:"We wrote a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribimos un libro.","Nosotras escribimos un libro.","Escribimos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas bebieron vino.", answers:["They drank wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They drank wine.", answers:["Ellas bebieron vino.","Ellos bebieron vino.","Bebieron vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I drank wine.", answers:["Yo bebí vino.","Bebí vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo bebí vino.", answers:["I drank wine."], language:"English"},			
	{question:"Tú leíste el libro.", answers:["You read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You read the book. (past tense)", answers:["Tú leíste el libro.","Leíste el libro.","Usted leyó el libro.","Ustedes leyeron el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escribieron.", answers:["The girls wrote.","The children wrote."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls wrote.", answers:["Las niñas escribieron."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ella era una persona.", answers:["She was a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"She was a person.", answers:["Ella era una persona.","Era una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leí.", answers:["I read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I read. (past tense)", answers:["Yo leí.","Leí."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño leyó.", answers:["The boy read.","The child read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy read.", answers:["El niño leyó."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Él era una persona.", answers:["He was a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"He was a person.", answers:["Él era una persona.","Era una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leímos un diario.", answers:["We read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We read a newspaper. (past tense)", answers:["Nosotros leímos un diario.","Nosotras leímos un diario.","Leímos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leyeron.", answers:["They read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They read. (past tense)", answers:["Ellas leyeron.","Ellos leyeron.","Leyeron."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leyeron un libro.", answers:["They read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They read a book. (past tense)", answers:["Ellas leyeron un libro.","Ellos leyeron un libro.","Leyeron un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotras comimos arroz.", answers:["We ate rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comimos arroz.", answers:["We ate rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We ate rice.", answers:["Nosotras comimos arroz.","Nosotros comimos arroz.","Comimos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cociné pescado.", answers:["I cooked fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I cooked fish.", answers:["Yo cociné pescado.","Cociné pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comieron nada.", answers:["They did not eat anything.","They didn't eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They did not eat anything.", answers:["Ellos no comieron nada.","Ellas no comieron nada.","No comieron nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cociné.", answers:["I did not cook.","I didn't cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I did not cook.", answers:["Yo no cociné.","No cociné."], language:"Spanish"}	

	
	]);	
